aloha-editor.org 2014-06-25

# Aloha Editor - HTML5 WYSIWYG Editor

    This privacy policy sets out how Gentics Software GmbH and this website  uses and
    protects any information that you give us when you use this website.
    
    Gentics Software GmbH is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask
    you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then
    you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
    
    Gentics Software GmbH may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You
    should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This
    policy is effective from 2010-07-15.
    
    What we collect
    
    We may collect the following information:
    
    .	contact information including email address
    .	demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
    .	other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
    
    What we do with the information we gather
    We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and
    in particular for the following reasons:
    
    .	Internal record keeping. 
    .	We may use the information to improve our products and services. 
    .	We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other
    	information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have
    	provided.  
    .	From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research
    	purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to
    	customise the website according to your interests.
    
    Security
    
    We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised
    access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial
    procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 
    
    How we use cookies
    
    A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once
    you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you
    visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The
    web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and
    remembering information about your preferences. 
    We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data
    about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only
    use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the
    system. 
    
    Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which
    pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer
    or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 
    You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies,
    but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may
    prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
    Links to other websites
    Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these
    links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
     Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information
    which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy
    statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the
    website in question.
    
    Controlling your personal information
    
    You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following
    ways:
    
    .	whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can
    	click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct
    	marketing purposes
    .	if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing
    	purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at aloha-sales@gentics.com 
    	We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have
    	your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send
    	you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you
    	tell us that you wish this to happen.
    	You may request details of personal information which we hold about you. A small fee will be payable.
    	If you would 	like a copy of the information 	held on you please write to Gentics Software GmbH, 
    	Gonzagagasse 11/25, A-1010 Vienna, 	Austria.If you believe that any information we are holding 
    	on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above 
    	address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
